Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
(This is a work of fiction)
(هذا عمل خيالي)
Shen Meng.
شين منغ.
Stop it.
اوقفها.
You can't wake her up.
لا يمكنك إيقاظها.
Let me get this straight.
دعني أفهم هذا الأمر بشكل صحيح.
You and Shen Meng are stuck on the same day...
أنت وشين مينغ عالقان في نفس اليوم...
because you broke up.
لأنك انفصلت.
To get out of this day,
للخروج من هذا اليوم،
you have to complete the mission given by the projector.
يتعين عليك إكمال المهمة التي أعطاها لك جهاز العرض.
You've already completed four levels...
لقد أكملت بالفعل أربعة مستويات...
of what was projected.
من ما كان متوقعا.
Now, it's the fifth level,
الآن، إنه المستوى الخامس،
kissing your ex.
تقبيل حبيبتك السابقة.
Dude.
يا صديقي.
I knew you're the only one...
لقد عرفت أنك الوحيد...
who would believe me.
من سيصدقني؟
I get it now.
لقد فهمت الآن.
Advanced intelligence.
ذكاء متقدم.
- Yes. - The Chosen One.
- نعم. - المختار.
- That's right. - An infinite loop, right?
- هذا صحيح. - حلقة لا نهائية، أليس كذلك؟
That's exactly it.
هذا هو بالضبط.
I understand your predicament.
أنا أفهم محنتك.
I won't stand by and do nothing.
لن أقف مكتوف الأيدي ولا أفعل شيئًا.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
What do you need me to do?
ماذا تريدني أن أفعل؟
Shen Meng deleted my Contacts before,
لقد قام شين منغ بحذف جهات الاتصال الخاصة بي من قبل،
so I don't have any contact information of my exes.
لذلك ليس لدي أي معلومات اتصال بأحبائي السابقين.
I do.
أفعل.
I'll contact her for you.
سأتصل بها من أجلك.
You're a good friend.
أنت صديق جيد.
What is your relationship...
ما هي علاقتك...؟
with the person who called the police, Zhao Ming Xi?
مع الشخص الذي اتصل بالشرطة، تشاو مينغ شي؟
He's my good friend.
إنه صديقي الجيد.
And why is Shen Meng,
ولماذا شين منغ،
the one lying on the bed, unconscious?
الذي يرقد على السرير فاقدًا للوعي؟
I'd better not tell you.
من الأفضل أن لا أخبرك.
This story is too ridiculous.
هذه القصة سخيفة للغاية.
You won't believe it even if I tell you.
لن تصدق حتى لو قلت لك.
You'll just laugh at me.
سوف تضحك علي فقط.
Are you questioning our professionalism?
هل تشكك في احترافيتنا؟
Tell us.
أخبرنا.
Say it!
قلها!
Chen Jia Wen.
تشن جيا ون.
I think...
أظن...
we shouldn't waste each other's time.
لا ينبغي لنا أن نضيع وقت بعضنا البعض.
I will...
أنا سوف...
- give you 10 more minutes. - Give you 10 more minutes.
- أعطيك 10 دقائق إضافية. - أعطيك 10 دقائق إضافية.
Wait.
انتظر.
How did you know what I'd say?
كيف عرفت ما سأقوله؟
Goodbye, officers.
وداعا أيها الضباط.
Time is almost up.
الوقت يقترب من الإنتهاء.
And your watch is ten seconds fast.
وساعتك أسرع بعشر ثواني.
We had a deal, okay?
لقد كان لدينا اتفاق، حسنًا؟
It's all for passing the level.
كل هذا من أجل اجتياز المستوى.
You can't blame me after waking up.
لا يمكنك إلقاء اللوم علي بعد الاستيقاظ.
You've had enough fun?
هل استمتعت بما فيه الكفاية؟
Don't explain.
لا تشرح.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
It's hard to give me up.
من الصعب أن تتخلى عني.
- Listen to me... - But no.
- استمع لي... - ولكن لا.
Chen Jia Wen,
تشن جيا ون,
you have to forget about me.
عليك أن تنساني.
We both need to start...
نحن بحاجة للبدء...
a new life.
حياة جديدة.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
But forgetting you is too hard for me.
لكن نسيانك صعب جدًا بالنسبة لي.
Every time I think about...
في كل مرة أفكر في...
our beautiful memories together, I'd feel like...
ذكرياتنا الجميلة معًا، أشعر وكأنني...
my heart is being torn apart.
قلبي يتمزق.
So,
لذا،
give me another chance.
أعطيني فرصة أخرى.
Okay?
تمام؟
Actually, I secretly made a vow...
في الواقع، لقد قطعت عهدًا سرًا...
that if you want to get back together with me within a year,
أنه إذا كنت تريد العودة معي خلال عام،
I would definitely say yes.
سأقول نعم بالتأكيد.
But now,
ولكن الآن،
it's too late.
لقد فات الأوان.
It's not too late.
لم يفت الوقت بعد.
You have to believe in our love.
يجب عليك أن تؤمن بمحبتنا.
It can transcend time,
يمكنه أن يتجاوز الزمن،
space, and reality.
الفضاء والواقع.
Everything can go back to how it used to be.
كل شيء يمكن أن يعود إلى ما كان عليه.
It's not too late for anything.
لم يفت الأوان بعد لأي شيء.
So trust me.
لذلك ثق بي.
Okay?
تمام؟
Do you think getting back together is that easy?
هل تعتقد أن العودة إلى بعضنا البعض أمر سهل؟
Pursue me again.
تابعني مرة أخرى.
We don't have to get back together yet,
ليس علينا أن نعود معًا بعد،
just kiss me!
فقط قبلني!
This...
هذا...
is my fault.
هذا خطئي.
- I shouldn't have come. - It's my fault.
- لم يكن ينبغي لي أن آتي. - إنه خطئي.
I shouldn't have asked to meet up.
لا ينبغي لي أن أطلب اللقاء.
I stooped so low too.
لقد انحنيت إلى أسفل أيضًا.
Why did I look at her phone for no reason?
لماذا نظرت إلى هاتفها بدون سبب؟
I don't usually look at it.
أنا لا أنظر إليه عادة.
Once I did, I saw it.
بمجرد أن فعلت ذلك، رأيته.
Man Li is my wife.
مان لي هي زوجتي.
As her husband,
كزوجها،
I have to deal with this.
يجب علي أن أتعامل مع هذا.
I understand.
أفهم.
I understand completely.
انا أفهم ذلك تماما.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Why do you want to meet her?
لماذا تريد مقابلتها؟
Dude, it's nothing, really.
يا رجل، إنه لا شيء حقًا.
Keep pretending.
استمر بالتظاهر.
You're still pretending with us?
هل مازلت تتظاهر معنا؟
You should know...
ينبغي عليك أن تعرف...
the kind of person Man Li is better than I do.
إن نوع الشخص الذي يعتبره مان لي أفضل مني.
In just going downstairs to pick up a package,
بمجرد النزول إلى الطابق السفلي لالتقاط الحزمة،
she can add three people on WeChat.
بإمكانها إضافة ثلاثة أشخاص على WeChat.
After just posting a selfie,
بعد نشر صورة شخصية للتو،
she'll get so many DMs.
ستحصل على عدد كبير جدًا من الرسائل المباشرة.
Tell me what it is.
أخبرني ما هو؟
I can handle it.
انا قادر على التعامل مع هذا الأمر.
Dude, I am...
يا رجل، أنا...
a bit short on cash lately.
لقد كان لدي القليل من النقود في الآونة الأخيرة.
I wanted to borrow some from her.
أردت أن أستعير بعضًا منها.
You want to borrow money?
هل تريد اقتراض المال؟
Who would believe that?
من يصدق ذلك؟
Dude.
يا صديقي.
You know...
أنت تعرف...
I...
أنا...
don't have it easy.
لا أجد الأمر سهلا.
Dude, have pity on me.
يا رجل، ارحمني.
I'm begging you.
انا أتوسل إليك.
Please don't contact my wife anymore, okay?
من فضلك لا تتصل بزوجتي مرة أخرى، حسنًا؟
Dude.
يا صديقي.
I'll delete her from my Contacts. I'll do it now.
سأحذفها من جهات اتصالي. سأفعل ذلك الآن.
I've deleted her.
لقد حذفتها.
Dude, you're so straightforward.
يا رجل، أنت صريح جدًا.
I feel so much better now.
أشعر بتحسن كبير الآن.
All right, I'll leave you to it.
حسنًا، سأتركك.
I still have a few more people to meet.
لا يزال أمامي لقاء المزيد من الأشخاص.
I have to deal with a few matters for her.
يجب علي أن أتعامل مع بعض الأمور بالنسبة لها.
Sit down.
اجلس.
Drink it all.
اشربها كلها
Take care, dude.
اعتني بنفسك يا صديقي.
Did you delete her alternate account?
هل قمت بحذف حسابها البديل؟
Dude, I don't have her alternate account.
يا رجل، ليس لدي حساب بديل لها.
Check it.
تحقق من ذلك.
I'm being narrow-minded.
أنا ضيق الأفق.
I'm so petty.
أنا تافهة جداً.
Sit down.
اجلس.
I didn't touch it. Drink it.
لم ألمسه. اشربه.
Message me if you need anything.
أرسل لي رسالة إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء.
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Come on.
تعال.
You...
أنت...
How should we kiss?
كيف يجب علينا التقبيل؟
For how long? With tongue?
إلى متى؟ باللسان؟
Do you know the rules?
هل تعرف القواعد؟
Is one kiss enough?
هل قبلة واحدة تكفي؟
I have a lot on my plate today.
لدي الكثير في طبقتي اليوم.
I don't have time for unrelated things.
ليس لدي وقت لأشياء غير ذات صلة.
I...
أنا...
Why don't we go to my place now?
لماذا لا نذهب إلى منزلي الآن؟
There's no need...
لا داعي...
Don't be shy with me.
لا تكن خجولا معي.
I'm not being shy.
أنا لا اكون خجولا.
Then what are you dilly-dallying for?
إذن لماذا تتلكأ؟
Saving her is more important.
إنقاذها هو الأهم.
Let's go to my place.
دعنا نذهب إلى مكاني.
Stop it. I'm not joking with you.
توقف، أنا لا أمزح معك.
Who's joking with you?
من يمزح معك؟
Forget it. I'll find someone else.
انسي الأمر، سأجد شخصًا آخر.
Stop.
قف.
Isn't it just a kiss?
أليست مجرد قبلة؟
It's no big deal.
إنها ليست مشكلة كبيرة.
I didn't think...
لم اظن...
you'd believe me.
ستصدقني.
With your brain,
مع عقلك،
you can't make up these lies.
لا يمكنك اختلاق هذه الأكاذيب.
But let me remind you.
ولكن دعني أذكرك.
If you really want to have a good relationship with her,
إذا كنت تريد حقًا أن تكون لديك علاقة جيدة معها،
don't say it was me.
لا تقل أنني كنت أنا.
You've had so much fun in the past couple of days, right?
لقد أمضيت وقتًا ممتعًا للغاية في اليومين الماضيين، أليس كذلك؟
You're free now.
أنت حر الآن.
And are you with Meng Meng now?
وهل أنت مع منغ منغ الآن؟
This is the kind of person you are. You're a jerk.
هذا هو نوع الشخص الذي أنت عليه. أنت أحمق.
You're a scumbag! Compensate me!
أنت حقير! عوضني!
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
Why are you eating popcorn?
لماذا تأكل الفشار؟
I brought you a late-night snack.
لقد أحضرت لك وجبة خفيفة في وقت متأخر من الليل.
It was Fang Zhi You, right?
لقد كان فانغ تشي يو، أليس كذلك؟
How did you know?
كيف عرفت؟
Aside from her,
بصرف النظر عنها،
who else would help you?
من غيره يمكنه مساعدتك؟
It's okay. We've already broken up.
لا بأس، لقد انفصلنا بالفعل.
It's all for passing the level.
كل هذا من أجل اجتياز المستوى.
I understand.
أفهم.
If I were dying,
لو كنت أموت،
and you must kiss your ex-boyfriend,
ويجب عليك تقبيل حبيبك السابق،
what would you do then?
ماذا ستفعل حينها؟
Don't change the subject.
لا تغير الموضوع
You're being unreasonable.
أنت غير معقول.
How long was I out?
كم من الوقت كنت بالخارج؟
Not long.
ليس طويلاً.
Not long?
ليس طويلا؟
Who was it? It went so well?
من كان؟ لقد سارت الأمور على ما يرام؟
You.
أنت.
- Me? - We've already broken up.
-أنا؟ - لقد انفصلنا بالفعل.
You're my ex-boyfriend.
أنت حبيبي السابق.
You could exploit a loophole like that?
هل يمكنك استغلال ثغرة كهذه؟